[
      {
        "question":"Expand the html shortcut.",
        "A": "Hyper Text Media Language",
        "B": "HyperText Markup Language",
        "C": "Hyper Tool Media Language",
        "D": "Hyper Translation Media Language",
        "correct": "B"
      },  
  
      {
        "question":"How to get a class element in JS",
        "A": "document.getElementsByClassName('class_name')",
        "B": "document.getElementById('id_name')",
        "C": "document.querySellector('selector_name')",
        "D": "document.getElementsByTagName(`tag_name`);",
        "correct": "A"
      }, 
      
      {
        "question":"How to declarte a constant variable?",
        "A": "let nameVariable;",
        "B": "constant nameVariable;",
        "C": "const nameVariable();",
        "D": "const nameVariable;",
        "correct": "D"
      },
      {
        "question":"Which loop/loop function will you use to add number every existing numbers in array?",
        "A": "array.forEach",
        "B": "if",
        "C": "do while",
        "D": "while",
        "correct": "A"
      },  
  
      {
        "question":"How to set direction on the y axis with flexbox css?",
        "A": "display: flex;",
        "B": "flex-wrap: nowrap",
        "C": "flex-direction: column",
        "D": "flex-flow: column wrap;",
        "correct": "C"
      }, 
      
      {
        "question":"How to set background color to div element when cursor is on it in css file?",
        "A": "div:hover {background: #@124532}",
        "B": "div:active {background: blue}",
        "C": "div:active {color: blue}",
        "D": "div:hover {background: red}",
        "correct": "D"
      },
      {
        "question":"How to get all elements of DOM element class=`triple`",
        "A": "document.querySelector(`.next-question`);",
        "B": "document.getSelectorAll(`.triple`);",
        "C": "document.querySelector(`.triple`);",
        "D": "document.querySelectorAll(`.triple`);",
        "correct": "D"
      },
      {
        "question":"Which selector is paragraph selector?`",
        "A": "<p>",
        "B": "<a>",
        "C": "<span>",
        "D": "<h1>",
        "correct": "A"
      },
      {
        "question":"how to declare a constant variable",
        "A": "let variable",
        "B": "variable constant",
        "C": "const variable",
        "D": "var variable;",
        "correct": "C"
      },
      {
        "question":"how to declare a constant variable",
        "A": "let variable",
        "B": "variable constant",
        "C": "const variable",
        "D": "var variable;",
        "correct": "C"
      },
      {
        "question":"how to remove eventlistener",
        "A": "addEventListener(`click``, (event) => {event.remove();})",
        "B": "addEventListener(`click`, nameofFunction)",
        "C": "removeEventListener(`click`, nameofFunction)",
        "D": "removeListener(`click`, nameofFunction)",
        "correct": "C"
      },
      {
        "question":"How to define flex in css",
        "A": "display:flex",
        "B": "display:flex-grid",
        "C": "display:grid",
        "D": "dissplay:block",
        "correct": "A"
      },
      {
        "question":"Does the condition have to be met in the if loop for the code to execute?",
        "A": "yes",
        "B": "no",
        "C": "The condition does not have to be fulfilled",
        "D": "I don't know",
        "correct": "A"
      },
      {
        "question":"You want to set the margin in pixels what command will you use in css",
        "A": "margin: 20rem",
        "B": "margin: 20px",
        "C": "padding: 20px",
        "D": "gap: 20px",
        "correct": "B"
      },
      {
        "question":"what method will you use to put something on the stack",
        "A": "add()",
        "B": "pop()",
        "C": "push()",
        "D": "delete()",
        "correct": "C"
      },
      {
        "question":"How to write the arrow function correctly",
        "A": "add()",
        "B": "hello = function() { return `Hello World!`; }",
        "C": "let myFunction = (a, b) => a * b;",
        "D": "function arrow() {return `hello world`}",
        "correct": "C"
      },
      {
        "question":"How to write random function in JS",
        "A": "radomize()",
        "B": "Marh.floor(Random());",
        "C": "Random(0,100)",
        "D": "Math.random() * 10",
        "correct": "D"
      }

      
  ]
